<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="0">
        <record id="customer_side_pending_stage" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">To Customer side pending</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="model_helpdesk_ticket"/>
<!--            <field name="email_from">${object.user_id.email_formatted}</field>-->
            <field name="email_to">${object.partner_email}</field>
            <field name="subject">Customer side pending stage</field>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="False"/>
            <field name="body_html" type="html">
                <div style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px;">
                    <p style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; font-size: 13px">
                        Dear ${object.partner_id.name}
                        <br> </br>
                        <br> </br>
                        Ticket No : ${object.id}
                        <br> </br>
                        I hope this email finds you well. We have been trying to reach you multiple times through 
                        various contact numbers provided, but unfortunately, we have not received any response.
                        <br> </br>
                        <br> </br>
                        We understand that your time is valuable, and we apologize for any inconvenience caused 
                        by our attempts to contact you. However, we believe it is essential to address this 
                        promptly and efficiently. To ensure a smooth resolution, we kindly request your confirmation 
                        for the field engineer visit.
                        <br> </br>
                        <br> </br>
                        Once we receive your confirmation, we will promptly align a qualified field engineer to visit 
                        your location at the earliest convenient time for you. Our dedicated team of experts is 
                        committed to delivering top-notch service and addressing any concerns you may have.
                        <br> </br>
                        <br> </br>
                        Please provide us with your preferred date and time for the field engineer visit, or let us
                        know if you require any assistance in scheduling the visit. You can reach us directly 
                        at 1800 419 3399 or reply to this email support@rdp.in
                        <br> </br>
                        <br> </br>
                        We sincerely appreciate your cooperation and look forward to resolving the matter efficiently.
                        If you have any questions or need further information, please do not hesitate to contact us.
                        <br></br>
                        <br></br>
                        Best regards,
                        <br> </br>
                        <br> </br>
                        RDP Helpdesk Team.
                        <br> </br>
                        1800 419 3399
                        <br> </br>
<!--                        <br> </br>-->
<!--                        Customer Service Department timings are Monday-Saturday, 10 AM-6 PM, on all working days-->
                    </p>
                </div>
            </field>
            <!--            <field name="report_template" ref="report_employee_card"/>-->
            <!--            <field name="report_name">Employee Card_${(object.name)}</field>-->
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>
